<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dry Bones</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dry Bones</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A website that points to the problems of the world and offers a solution, unheard of by most. Using the teachings of Jesus and bible prophesy as a lense in which to view the world and how the future is unfolding.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;Contact us&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:reachthewholeworld@gmail.com&#34;&gt;reachthewholeworld@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insignificant?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/insignificant/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/09/insignificant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Maybe not every task needs to be monumental. Perhaps the little things in life, the things we won’t remember, are what will count most. We’d like to think we’ll be remembered by the great things we do, the daring, the brave, but what most sums up each of us is the small qualities that continuously show themselves each and every day.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For the most part, the great people are never born great, slaying dragons, rescuing princesses, saving the day. They have spent most of their life preparing, gaining wisdom, increasing daily in discipline and then, when the opportunity arises they show their colors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I understand things - a ramble</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/how-i-understand-things-a-ramble/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/how-i-understand-things-a-ramble/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello, it seemed appropriate to me to write something about how I understand life, its purpose, and our reasons for existence. Not to say that you need to think like me, but I guess to share so you know where I’m coming from. Take what you like and throw away what you don’t, but I hope that some of this helps you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I wasn’t sure why I was here at first, or what my purpose was, but after living for a while I discovered a man’s teachings unlike any other through a Youtube Channel. I tried to implement those teachings in my life as best I could, and came to see them as true. These teachings I am refering to are the ones that come from Jesus in the bible. I saw that what he taught was ignored by churches and people of all different backgrounds, and after implementing them in my life I started to see the reason for Jesus’ teachings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Characteristics of the mark</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/characteristics-of-the-mark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 18:34:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/characteristics-of-the-mark/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;RedScaryImage&#34; src=&#34;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1604063176436-b463de60413f?q=80&amp;w=2328&amp;auto=format&amp;fit=crop&amp;ixlib=rb-4.0.3&amp;ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-will-the-mark-be-like&#34;&gt;What will the mark be like?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The mark of the beast, what is it and what characteristics will it most likely have?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The mark of the beast is a mark which everyone will be required to have in order to buy and sell. It’s not clear when the mark will come or exactly what it will look like, but from its description in Revelation 13:16-17 we’ve done our best to try and piece together a rough idea of the characteristics and qualities the mark will probably have.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worldcoin - the solution of the future?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/worldcoin-the-solution-of-the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/08/worldcoin-the-solution-of-the-future/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Worldcoin Logo&#34; src=&#34;https://worldcoin-company-website.cdn.prismic.io/worldcoin-company-website/ZxFd_IF3NbkBXsKH_World_logo-01-4-.svg?w=2560&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-is-world-coin&#34;&gt;WHAT IS WORLD COIN?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Worldcoin (now know as world) is a digital crypto currency made to be usable anywhere in the world which already has 2 million people register for it and has received over one hundred and fifty million dollars in funding backed by some big names in the tech and AI industry. It’s supposed to be an inclusive, universal, secure, crypto currency and it’s linked to a digital ID generated from a user’s biometric data, an ID which is required to have if you want to buy or sell using the currency.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
