<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2023-09-06T17:06:59+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Drybones | Blog</title><subtitle>Points to the problems of the world and offer a solution unheard of by most.</subtitle><author><name>Ezekiel</name></author><entry><title type="html">How I understand things - a ramble</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/08/30/How-I-see-things/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="How I understand things - a ramble" /><published>2023-08-30T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2023-08-30T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/08/30/How-I-see-things</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/08/30/How-I-see-things/"><![CDATA[<p>Hello, person. It seemed appropriate to me to write something about how I
understand life, its purpose, and our reasons for existence. Not to say that
you need to think like me, but I guess to share so you know where I’m coming
from. Take what you like and throw away what you don’t, but I hope that some of
this helps you.</p>

<p>I wasn’t sure why I was here at first, or what my purpose was, but after living
for a while I discovered a man’s teachings unlike any other through a Youtube
Channel. I tried to implement those teachings in my life as best I could, and
came to see them as true. These teachings I am refering to are the ones that
come from Jesus in the bible. I saw that what he taught was ignored by churches
and people of all different backgrounds, and after implementing them in my life
I started to see the reason for Jesus’ teachings.</p>

<p>Jesus teaches that if you want to follow him we must forsake all that we own,
for example, and at first I just didn’t understand why. WHY did I need to give
up all I own? Why did I need to stop working for money, like he said to do in
Matthew 6? What good would it do?</p>

<p>Now I see though that Jesus didn’t come to tell us to do meaningless or
purposeless rules as a shit test in life like most people think God does. “Eat
this cracker”, “Drink this juice”, “Pay tithes to the church”, etc. That isn’t
what Jesus taught and isn’t the type of meaningless stuff that he wants us to
do.</p>

<p>He came to build something called the kingdom of heaven. This isn’t some
kingdom in the clouds where we recline on white fluff while babyfaced angels
feed us grapes and play harps, this is a government that he came to build here
on earth. One that anyone can help build and that requires human effort and
cooperation to bring about.</p>

<p>I believe that it’s our purpose as humans to bring about that kingdom. And,
only when necessary will God ever step in to help. I believe he’s mainly
leaving it up to us to build it, so we can learn and develop ourselves.</p>

<p>For now he’s in the recruiting stages of his kingdom, where he’s seeing who
puts their trust in him, in the truth, and in love and justice, and lives for
those values regardless of if those around them do or not. You don’t want your
kingdom full of cowards, whimps, and liars, and so in some sense I do believe
this life is a test, but one that isn’t a waste of time. We’ll be able to keep
whatever we learn here. Whatever skills we develop we’ll take with us when
we’re resurrected.</p>

<p>I can’t say I know for sure exactly what happens after that but I do know that
for 1,000 years 140,000 followers of his will help him rule the earth due to
what it says in the book of Revelation. I think during this time we’ll be able
to have a fresh start and be given the ability to literally bring “heaven” to
earth. That being said, I also believe that if we humans get our act together
now we could bring heaven to earth now rather than later. The problem is we
face opposition.</p>

<p>The shortsighted, the greedy, the envious, and our own wants and desires
prevent us from striving to build this kingdom that will last forever. The men
and women who want to bring about this world of peace where no one lacks and
everyone has what they need, are confronted by those who want more than their
fair-share. Most people in the world today fall in that category, and if we’re
not careful even we ourselves fall into that category at times. That’s I think
why we need to forsake all we own. To give away our possessions and lay all our
hopes and dreams on the alter. God asked that much of his first follower,
Abraham, and he doesn’t ask any less of us.</p>

<p>If we can muster up the faith and courage to act on God’s will, then doing so
will allow us to successfully bring about heaven on earth, even if it’s just a
little section of it. Otherwise we may find ourselves fighting against the very
kingdom of God.</p>

<p>Are you interested in building God’s kingdom? It’s not one that can be observed
but rather one that resides in the hearts of men and comes about through love,
truth, and justice. If you want to build that kingdom then I recommend that you
read through Jesus teachings. A place to get started reading is Matthew chapter
5, 6, and 7.</p>

<p>Building God’s kingdom will take a life time, constant openness to God’s voice,
a humble and contrite heart, and a desire to do what right even if it doesn’t
benefit ourselves. Do you feel that God is calling you to to be part of such a
kingdom, his kingdom?</p>

<hr />

<p>Get in contact here: 
<a href="https://drybones37.github.io./about/">Contact Info</a></p>]]></content><author><name>Ezekiel</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, person. It seemed appropriate to me to write something about how I understand life, its purpose, and our reasons for existence. Not to say that you need to think like me, but I guess to share so you know where I’m coming from. Take what you like and throw away what you don’t, but I hope that some of this helps you.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What we know about the mark</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/08/17/What-can-we-inferr-about-the-mark/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What we know about the mark" /><published>2023-08-17T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2023-08-17T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/08/17/What-can-we-inferr-about-the-mark</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/08/17/What-can-we-inferr-about-the-mark/"><![CDATA[<p align="center">
<img src="https://www.artificialintelligence-news.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/9/2023/08/sec-gary-gensler-ai-artificial-intelligence-legal-law-finance-automation-768x511.jpg" alt="Worldcoin Logo" />
</p>

<pre>
</pre>
<h3 id="what-will-the-mark-be-like">What will the mark be like?</h3>
<pre>
</pre>

<hr />

<p>The mark of the beast, what is it and what characteristics
will it most likely have?</p>

<p>The mark of the beast is a mark which everyone will be
required to have in order to buy and sell. It’s not clear when
the mark will come or exactly what it will look like, but from
its description in Revelation 13:16-17 we’ve done our best to
try and piece together a rough idea of the characteristics and
qualities the mark will probably have.</p>

<p>Before we dive in, here is the description of the mark from
the thirteenth chapter of the Revelation.</p>

<pre>

</pre>

<blockquote style="text-align: justify;">
"He caused all people, great and small, rich and poor, free and slave, to receive a mark on their right hand or on their forehead, so that they could not buy or sell unless they had the mark, or the name of the beast, or the number of its name." 
</blockquote>
<p><cite style="text-align: right; display: block;"><a href="https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=Revelation+13%3A16-17&amp;version=KJV" target="_blank">- Revelation 13:16-17 </a></cite></p>

<pre>
</pre>

<p>From the description about the mark we can conclude a few
things right off the bat.</p>

<pre>
</pre>

<h4 id="guarantees">Guarantees</h4>
<ul>
  <li>The mark of the beast will be in the right hand or forehead.</li>
  <li>The mark will be used for buying and selling.</li>
  <li>If you don’t have the mark you won’t be able to buy or sell.</li>
  <li>The mark is meant for everyone, “all”.</li>
</ul>

<p>From these Guarantees we can conclude a few other things that
I will also call guarantees.</p>

<ul>
  <li>Since you can’t buy or sell without the mark, every seller will need to be able to determine if you have the mark or not, even online retailers.</li>
  <li>The mark will need to be accessible to everyone in the world.</li>
  <li>The mark will be some form of computer technology, otherwise it’d be unfeasible to implement on a global scale.</li>
</ul>

<p>Now I think these three concluded guarantees have immense
implications for the mark. The implications of the three
things I just mentioned lead me to believe when the mark comes
it will have these next few qualities. The mark would need to
be <strong>unforgeable, unstealable, undupicatable, unhackable, yet
always recoverable.</strong></p>

<pre>
</pre>

<h4 id="reasoning">Reasoning</h4>
<p>Why would it need to have those qualities?
If you are going to convince billions of people to take the
mark with as little resistance as possible, (which I assume is
the goal) they’ll have to be certain that all of their money
is safe and will always be safe while using the mark system.
If the mark is the only thing you can use in order to buy and
sell then all of their money and accounts will need to be
linked to the mark in some way. So, if it were to get
destroyed in a car wreck or accident, forcefully removed by a
crook, duplicated by a thief, or hacked by a hacker, you’d
have to have a way to stop or prevent any of that from
affecting the mark bearer’s wealth, or from it happening in
the first place.</p>

<p>The only real way you could make sure that the mark is
unstealable, unduplicateable, unhackable, yet always
recoverable is to tie each mark to a person’s biometric data,
like their DNA. This way the mark could only work if it was in
the proper owner’s hand or forehead, and even if the mark was
duplicated it wouldn’t work without the owner’s biometric
data, possibly DNA, present.</p>

<pre>
</pre>

<h4 id="recoverability">Recoverability</h4>
<p>Regarding the need to make the mark always recoverable, if
someone was in an accident for instance, and their hand was
crushed along with their mark, then they’d need to be able to
recover their money somehow. If the mark was linked to their
biometrics data  they could go to a recovery office of some
sort and let them scan their biometric data to recover their
account and to get a replacement mark. So, that would ensure
even if the mark was destroyed their wealth wouldn’t be. This
NECESSITATES that the mark be tied to a person’s biometric
data. Otherwise if the chip was destroyed then they’d lose
access to all of their funds and have no way of recovering
their money except by extremely less fraud proof methods, like
word of mouth or ID’s.</p>

<p>In order to maintain the qualities of the mark being
unstealable, unhackable, unduplicatable, yet always
recoverable, I think the mark system would also NEED to
prohibit anyone who hasn’t registered for a mark from buying
and selling on the mark system. This means that computers
won’t have the ability to buy or sell things on the mark
system, UNLESS, a person with a mark gives them permission to
do so for that specific transaction. (This would ensure that
those without a mark couldn’t buy or sell even with a
computer, staying true to the mark’s description in Revelation
13.)</p>

<pre>
</pre>

<h4 id="fraud-prevention">Fraud Prevention</h4>
<p>In order to stop computers, hackers, or people who don’t have
the mark, from buying or selling things online, this would
also NECESSITATE that a person tie their biometric data with
their mark. Requiring biometric data to use the mark and not
allowing any duplicates would help ensure the system that
anyone using the mark system to buy and sell is someone the
system can trust and not a bad actor or hacker. If the mark
wasn’t tied to a person’s biometric data lots of fraud, theft,
and money laundering would take place like we see with online
money and cryptocurrencies nowadays, since none of it is tied
to an online users actual identity.</p>

<p>On the other hand, I think the mark will most likely run on
block chain technology, but to prevent fraud, scams, and theft,
each account holder on the mark system’s block chain would have
their account linked to a biometric digital ID. This ensures
that each and every transaction would be traceable and
transparent. Thus disallowing anyone from exchanging money
secretly or engaging in fraudulent activity.</p>

<p>If the mark didn’t have people’s biometric data linked to it,I
think much of the public wouldn’t put much faith in it because
then it would be easier to steal, duplicate, forge, and would
be much harder to recover. If the mark doesn’t offer anyone
any more financial security than they already have then why
would they get it? If you want people to adopt new technology
then something has to be in it for them or it’s going to be an
uphill battle from the start.</p>

<pre>
</pre>

<h4 id="perks-of-the-mark">Perks of the Mark</h4>
<p>From the perspective of someone who is either creating the
mark or wanting to sell it to the public, if they make the
system have the characteristics and qualities along the lines
of what I’ve mentioned prior, that will give the users LOTS of
perks compared to the current economic system.</p>

<p>With the mark you’d essentially be unrobable, monetarily. If
someone does rob you it couldn’t be your money, or the
transaction would be traceable and they’d be caught. Same for
if someone scammed you.</p>

<p>If governments are distributing welfare programs the mark
would also server to prevent corrupt officials from siphoning
funds to secret private bank accounts and instead ensure that
whatever money is set aside for welfare programs goes to the
people it’s intended to go to.</p>

<p>Transferring money to anyone would be possible from anywhere.
So if someone from India wants to send money to a relative in
the UK, they could do so almost instantly and seamlessly using
the mark system.</p>

<p>Honestly, compared to the current system there are a fair
number of benefits that a mark of the beast system could bring
about to the current financial systems in place, and that’s
why I think most people will take it.</p>

<p>That being said, I think there is an even better “financial”
or “economic” system out there than any monetary one, but
that’s for another article.</p>

<pre>
</pre>

<h4 id="conclusion">Conclusion</h4>

<p>In sum, I personally believe that the mark will come about and have these characteristics:
	* You won’t be able to buy or sell if you don’t have the mark.
	* It will be a mark in the right hand or forehead.
	* It will be a form of computer technology.
	* It will be tied to a person’s biometric data.
	* It will operate on block chain technology.
	* In order to buy and sell on the mark system the system will first need your biometric data.</p>

<p>Now, regardless of how many of these characteristics I’ve
shared are certain, there is ONE characteristic of the mark that
IS a certainty, that is we won’t be able to buy or sell if we
don’t have the mark.</p>

<p>Knowing this certainty I hope that each of us seeks God’s will
for how we live our lives now. If we keep our hearts and minds
open to God showing us ways to live without needing a paying
job or money NOW then I think we’ll all be much better
prepared when the mark comes.</p>

<p>If you’d like to find out more about how to prepare to live without the mark feel free to write to the email 
<a href="https://drybones37.github.io./about/">on the about page here.</a></p>

<p>Thank you for reading.</p>

<hr />

<!--
##### Index:
Post ideas:
* What we can infer about the mark.
* 


-->]]></content><author><name>Ezekiel</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Worldcoin - the solution of the future?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2023/08/11/Worldcoin/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Worldcoin - the solution of the future?" /><published>2023-08-11T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2023-08-11T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2023/08/11/Worldcoin</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2023/08/11/Worldcoin/"><![CDATA[<!--
##### Index:

[WHAT IS WORLDCOIN?](#what-is-world-coin)

[WORLDCOIN'S SIMILARITIES TO THE MARK](#worldcoins-similarities-to-the-mark)

[WORLDCOIN’S MARKETING](#worldcoins-marketing)

[A CO-FOUNDER OF WORLDCOIN](#a-co-founder-of-worldcoin)

[THE SOLUTION](#the-solution)
-->
<p align="center">
<img src="https://image.coinpedia.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/24192722/Worldcoin-img.webp" alt="Worldcoin Logo" />
</p>
<hr />
<pre>
</pre>
<h5 id="what-is-world-coin">WHAT IS WORLD COIN?</h5>
<pre>
</pre>

<p>Worldcoin is a digital crypto currency made to be usable anywhere in the world which already has 2 million people register for it and has received over one hundred and fifty million dollars in funding backed by some big names in the tech and AI industry. It’s supposed to be an inclusive, universal, secure, crypto currency and it’s linked to a digital ID generated from a user’s biometric data, an ID which is required to have if you want to buy or sell using the currency.</p>

<p>This Identifier or for Worldcoin is called a “World ID”. The way you get it is you allow your irises in your eyes to be scanned by a machine they themselves call “The Orb”, an iris biometric data scanning device they made. They then use the biometric data from your irises as a way to verify that you are a unique human.</p>

<p>Worldcoin was made on the premise that eventually AI will become so good at pretending to be human that more advanced ID systems will need to be made to verify that users online ARE human. They fear the current world financial system is at risk of being manipulated by those who will control AI if such an ID system isn’t put in place, and they think the biometric digital passport, the “World ID”, will serve that purpose of determining who is human and who isn’t.</p>

<p>One way or another, they say, a world biometric proof of personhood, a “World ID”,  is inevitable, and so instead of letting an evil government build it, they themselves decided to build it and assure us that once the system is in place they’ll distribute power equally and fairly to all…</p>
<pre>
</pre>

<pre>

</pre>

<blockquote style="text-align: center;">“Something like World ID will need to happen,”
</blockquote>
<p><cite style="text-align: right; display: block;"><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/24/the-untold-story-of-worldcoins-launch-inside-the-orb/" target="_blank"> Alex Blania - Co-founder of Worldcoin</a></cite></p>

<pre>

</pre>

<h5 id="worldcoins-similarities-to-the-mark">WORLDCOIN’S SIMILARITIES TO THE MARK</h5>
<pre>
</pre>

<p>Those behind Worldcoin think they’re helping humanity, but if any of you are familiar with the description about the mark of the beast in the bible, what they’re saying should be very alarming.</p>
<pre>
</pre>

<h6 id="revelation-1316-17">Revelation: 13:16-17:</h6>
<p>“It caused ALL people, great and small, rich and poor, free and slave, to receive a mark on their right hand or on their forehead, so that they could not buy or sell unless they had the mark, which is the name of the beast or the number of its name.”
<cite><a href="https://www.biblegateway.com/passage/?search=Revelation+13%3A16-17&amp;version=KJV" target="_blank"> Revelation 13:16-17 </a></cite></p>

<pre>
</pre>

<p>Worldcoin is laying down the groundwork for a global financial system that seems like it could eventually lead to just that! Read their mission statement,</p>

<pre>

</pre>

<blockquote style="text-align: center;">“Something like World ID will need to happen,”
"The mission of the Worldcoin project is to build the world’s largest identity AND financial network as a public utility, giving ownership to EVERYONE." </blockquote>
<p><cite style="text-align: right; display: block;"><a href="https://whitepaper.worldcoin.org/tokenomics" target="_blank">Worldcoin</a></cite></p>

<pre>

</pre>

<p>In other words, it’s supposed to be a global financial AND identity system for ALL, that you can ONLY use if you allow your eyeballs to be scanned.</p>

<p>So, for example, if a country were to switch to Worldcoin as their state currency and stop using physical cash, as a by-product that WOULD CAUSE ALL, people in their country, to either scan their eyes or be excluded from their own countries economy.</p>

<p>Now, I’m not saying that Worldcoin IS the mark, but the system they are setting up for Worldcoin sure seems eerily similar. They aren’t asking for a mark in the right hand or forehead, but perhaps with time they’ll find that iris scans won’t work for all people, like those who suffer eye damage after signing up and can’t recover their account.</p>

<pre>

</pre>
<h5 id="worldcoins-marketing">WORLDCOIN’S MARKETING</h5>
<pre>
</pre>
<p>On top of all of this Worldcoin is being sold to the public as a potential solution to some of the fundamental problems of the world like the distribution of power and resources, and hints at possibly being the monetary framework that would allow for a Universal Basic Income, potentially distributed by an AI.</p>
<pre>
</pre>

<pre>

</pre>
<blockquote style="text-align: center;">
"Worldcoin could significantly increase equality of opportunity globally by advancing a future where everyone, regardless of their location, can participate in the global digital economy through universally-accessible decentralized financial and identity infrastructure. As the network grows, so should its utility."
</blockquote>
<p><cite style="text-align: right; display: block;"><a href="https://whitepaper.worldcoin.org/" target="_blank"> Worldcoin</a></cite></p>

<blockquote style="text-align: center;">
"Furthermore, World ID can also enable global democratic processes and novel forms of governance (e.g., via quadratic voting), and it may eventually support a path to AI-funded Universal Basic Income."
</blockquote>
<p><cite style="text-align: right; display: block;"><a href="https://whitepaper.worldcoin.org/tokenomics" target="_blank"> Worldcoin - Tokenomics</a></cite></p>

<pre>

</pre>

<p>What Worldcoin is claiming that it will offer the potential to revolutionize the current systems that mankind have in place for governing ourselves, buying and selling, and making and doing business. But will Worldcoin, or any global economic and identity system made and created by humans really be able to overcome the problems that plague humanity?</p>
<pre>

</pre>

<h5 id="the-co-founder-of-worldcoin">THE CO-FOUNDER OF WORLDCOIN</h5>
<pre>
</pre>

<p>Take a look at the track record of the Co-founder of Worldcoin himself, Sam Altman, to see the direction Worldcoin will most likely take in the future.</p>

<p>He is the co-founder of Worldcoin and the current CEO of OpenAI. – <em>OpenAI is the company that owns and opperates ChatGPT, the AI chatbot.</em> – He ironically, helped start OpenAI in 2015 as a nonprofit research organization committed to advancing digital intelligence for the benefit of humanity, promising to be transparent and share their findings with the world.</p>

<p>Fast-forward to today though, and OpenAI is now a profit-driven company in bed with Microsoft sharing very little if any of their findings with anyone.</p>

<p>If Sam Altman’s track record says anything, it’s that his ideals, like most others’, quickly fall to the wayside once money gets involved. Besides that his company “Worldcoin” even admits that they are making the biometric ID only because they think someone worse than them will make it in the future if they don’t.</p>

<pre>

</pre>

<pre>
</pre>

<blockquote style="text-align: center;">
"But the biggest risk, as the company’s braintrust sees it, is not a risk about Worldcoin itself. The most chilling risk, to them, is that something like a biometric World ID will be developed, only not in a way that’s open or privacy-preserving."
</blockquote>
<p><cite style="text-align: right; display: block;"><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/24/the-untold-story-of-worldcoins-launch-inside-the-orb/" target="_blank"> Coindesk</a></cite></p>

<pre>

</pre>

<blockquote style="text-align: center;">
“I think Worldcoin is the only other path there is.”
</blockquote>
<p><cite style="text-align: right; display: block;"><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/24/the-untold-story-of-worldcoins-launch-inside-the-orb/" target="_blank">Alex Blania - Co-founder of Worldcoin</a></cite></p>

<pre>


</pre>

<p>They are convinced that the only way forward for humanity, the solution, is a universal global economic and identification system in which you need to allow biometric data to be taken from you in order to buy and sell and they don’t see another way. Alex Blania, the other Co-founder of Worldcoin, also thinks this and this will be the same conclusion that most other people in the world will arrive at, because they think it’s the only way.</p>

<pre>

</pre>
<h5 id="the-solution">THE SOLUTION</h5>
<pre>
</pre>

<p>BUT, there is another way. The other way is that humans share… and instead of putting our trust in our own creations like the idol worshippers of the past did, we put our faith in a loving God. The one who he sent his son to share his simple solution to the problems we face today almost two millennia ago.</p>

<p>His son said, “You cannot serve two masters. You will hate one and love the other, or despise one and admire the other. You cannot serve BOTH God and money.” Yet the human race goes on working for money. If the human race would stop working for money and share all they have with one another there would be no NEED for money, or Worldcoin. Sharing doesn’t require money, onlylove. And that’s what God is.</p>

<p>So if the human race would focus on serving God and our fellow humans we WOULD be able to solve all of the world’s problems, but only IF we listen to him and to his son’s teachings.</p>

<p>To hear more about how the world could be if everyone listened to Jesus teachings, click the link to this article: <cite><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/consensus-magazine/2023/07/24/the-untold-story-of-worldcoins-launch-inside-the-orb/" target="_blank">A World Without Money</a></cite></p>

<p>So which will it be, Love, or money?</p>

<p>One will lead to a global world ID and financial system in which you’ll need to register for in order to buy and sell, while the other will lead to a global system built on trust in a loving creator held together by a volunteer workforce motivated by love.</p>

<p>If you choose the latter please stay in touch and write to us if you want. We’d love to hear from you.</p>

<pre>


</pre>

<p>Email: 
<a href="https://drybones37.github.io./about/">Contact Info</a></p>

<hr />]]></content><author><name>Ezekiel</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[&lt;!– Index:]]></summary></entry></feed>